Jordan Bradfield







jordanbradfield.ca 🌎 Halifax, Nova Scotia 🔌 +1 (902) 521 0515



ABOUT ME

I (Jordan Bradfield) am an Intermediate level Full Stack Javascript Developer with 3+ years experience. I am currently working as an Application developer at IBM. I'm role agnostic and have experience as a developer, lead developer and team lead. I have a great personality, high motivation and a hunger for success. I strive to learn more and become better every day.

EXPERIENCE

IBM (June 2017 - Present)

At this role I worked primarily as a Full Stack Web and Hybrid Mobile Developer. Working as a lead developer to deliver a Mobile Solution for IOS/Android with a single code base using web technologies.

TECH STACK

- Angular + AngularJS + Cordova + React
- + Redux + Node + Webpack + Grunt
- + LESS/SASS + Angular Material
- React Material + HTML/CSS

IBM CO-OP (May 2016 - August 2016)

At this role I was assigned to build a MEAN stack Web Application as an internal IBM Project. I worked with a colleague to deliver a Full Stack Web Application using SSO, Socket.io and Web Mailing Services.

TECH STACK

- + AngularJS + Node + ExpressJS + Socket.io
- + MongoDB + Cloudant + Bluemix + NoSQL
- + Passport + Bootstrap + HTML/CSS
- + Node Mailer

EDUCATION

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Database Administration

NSCC (IT campus) - Halifax, Nova Scotia

September 2015 - June 2017

JAVA BOOTCAMP

Full Stack Concentration

NSCC (IT campus) - Halifax, Nova Scotia

August 2017 - September 2017

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

- > Accessibility
- > Angular
- > AngularJS
- > Ajax/XHR
- > Cordova
- > Express
- > HTML/CSS
- > Javascript

- > Less/Sass
- > Material Design
- > Node
- > React
- > Responsive (Flex)
- > Source Control (Git)
- > Webpack/Grunt
- Unit Testing (Jest)

GENERAL

- Agile
- Collaboration
- Communication
- Design Thinking
- Kanban
- Openness
- Organization
- Pair Programming

- Prioritization
- Reliable
- Role Agnostic
- Scrum
- SDLC
- Self Learner
- Time Management
- Waterfall

Github: github.com/javascript-jordan